Sheet Music Collection
Sheet Music Collection
- Sheet music
  - Lesser-known composers
    - Trotère, H. In Old Madrid, arranged by N. Clifford Page, vocal (choral with piano accompaniment) two copies, one marked "Beal" (Oversize 12)
    - Trotère, H. In Old Madrid, words by Clifton Bingham, vocal (song) ("Conrad" written on cover) (Oversize 12)
    - Turner-Maley, Florence Then Easter Day was Born, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (high voice) (Oversize 12)
    - Tucker, Henry Sweet Genevieve, words by George Cooper, vocal (song) (Oversize 12)
    - Van de Water, Beardsley Offertory Solos: The Good Shepherd, vocal (song) (high voice) two copies, both signed by Winifred S. Myers (Oversize 12)
    - Van de Water, Beardsley Night of Nights, arranged as a duet by Charles Fonteyn Manney, vocal (duet) (soprano and tenor) (Oversize 12)
    - Van der Stucken, Frank Our Glorious Land, vocal (choral) (piano accompaniment for rehearsal only), cover with red, two copies (Oversize 12)
    - Van der Stucken, Frank Our Glorious Land, vocal (choral) (piano accompaniment for rehearsal only), cover with no red, two copies (Oversize 12)
    - Viereck, J. C. Marche Favorite de l'Opera de Bellini Norma (Op. 31), piano (four hands) (Oversize 12)
    - Voelker Schottische: Frolics of the Sylphs, (orchestral sheet music) (bottoms not cut) (Oversize 12)
    - Von Flotow, Friedrich May Gentle Sleep Fall O'er Thee: Nocturne from "Martha" Act II, English version by M. Barnett, vocal (choral with organ accompaniment) (Oversize 12)
    - Von Scriba, J. Mefistofele Grand Trio pour Piano, Violon et Violoncelle sur des motifs de l'Opéra de Boito par J. Von Scriba, piano trio (piano, violin, cello) (Oversize 12)
    - Von Tilzer, Albert Oh Gee, Say Gee, You Ought to See My Gee Gee from the Fiji Isles, words by Lew Brown, vocal (song) (Oversize 12)
    - Waldteufel, Emile Espana Waltz, arr. by Franz Mahl (orchestral sheet music) (Oversize 13)
    - Waldteufel, Emile L'Estudiantina Waltz, revised by S. K. Wright (orchestral sheet music) three folders (Oversize 13)
    - Waldteufel, Emile L'Esprit Française Polka, (orchestral sheet music) (Oversize 13)
    - Waldteufel, Emile Manola Waltzes, keyboard (solo) (Oversize 13)
    - Waldteufel, Emile Mon rêve, keyboard (solo) (Oversize 13)
    - Wallerstein, A. Brigand Polka, piano (solo) (Oversize 13)
    - Walsh, B. The Helmsman's Song, words by M. J. O'Sullivan, Esqr., vocal (song) (Oversize 13)
    - Ward-Stephens Hail! Thou Risen One, words by Rev. A. Edwin Keigwin, vocal (song with organ accompaniment) (high voice) three copies, one signed "Mrs. Myers" (Oversize 13)
    - Warren, Harry When the Shepherd Leads the Sheep Back Home, words by Edgar Leslie, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (optional ukulele or banjulele bajo accompaniment) (Oversize 13)
    - Watson, M. The King's Champion, arr. for the Coda by G. A. Veazie, vocal (choral) (Oversize 13)
    - Weeks, Harold Chong (He Come from Hong Kong), arr. by William Schulz (orchestral sheet music) (Oversize 13)
    - Weil, O. In Autumn/Herbstfrühlingslied, vocal (song with piano and violin accompaniment) (Oversize 13)
    - Weiland, F. The Guitarist's Repertoire: No. 1, Tis the Harp in the Air, composed by W. V. Wallace, vocal (song with guitar accompaniment) (Oversize 13)
    - Weill, Irving Tripoli: On the Shores of Tripoli, lyric by Paul Cunningham & Al Dubin, vocal (song) (Oversize 13)
    - Weiss, Julius Ouverturen aus beliebten Opern: no. 3: Die Stumme von Portici von Auber (Op. 70), piano trio (piano, violin, and cello) (Oversize 13)
    - Weiss, Julius Ouverturen aus beliebten Opern: no. 37: Die lustigen Weiber von Windsor von O. Nicolai (Op. 70), violin (duet with keyboard accompaniment) (Oversize 13)
    - Weiss, Julius Ouverturen aus beliebten Opern: no. 40: Preciosa von Carl Maria von Weber (Op. 70), violin (duet with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 13)
    - Weiss, Julius - Ouverturen aus beliebten Opern: no. 50: Si j'étais Roi von Adam (Op. 70), piano trio (violin, cello, and piano) (Oversize 13)
    - Wely, Lefebure Titania Fantaisie de Concert, keyboard (solo) (Oversize 13)
    - Wendling, Pete Oh! What a Pal Was Mary, words by Edgar Leslie and Bert Kalmar, arr. by Fred E. Ahlert vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 13)
    - Wentworth, C. C. Gracie and Gertie Galop for four hands, piano (four hands) (Oversize 13)
    - White, C. A. When ‘Tis Moonlight, vocal (song) (soprano) (Oversize 13)
    - White, Maude Valérie The Throstle, words by Tennyson, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (soprano) (signed "Winifred S. Myers") (Oversize 13)
    - Whitely, Bessie M. The Shadows, words by Frank L. Stanton, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) ("Frank L. Stanton – M. 1972" written on cover) (Oversize 13)
    - Whiteman, Paul Wonderful One, words by Dorothy Terriss, music also by Ferdie Grofé, adapted from a Theme by Marshall Neilar, vocal (song) (Oversize 13)
    - Whiting, Richard A. The Japanese Sandman, told by Raymond B. Egan, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 13)
    - Wiegand, John Piano Transcriptions: Old Folks at Home (S. C. Foster), piano (solo) ("L. S. S…" written on cover) (Oversize 13)
    - Williams, T. Vocal Duets by Celebrated Composers: Larboard Watch, vocal (duet) (medium voices) (Oversize 13)
    - Williams, W. Cujus Animam: the Celebrated Aria from Rossini's Stabat Mater, arranged with variations for the pianoforte, piano (solo) (Oversize 13)
    - Wilson, Ira Bishop Brave Pure and True: Patriotic Solo, words by Edith Sanford Tillotson, vocal (song) (medium voice) (Oversize 13)
    - Winner, Sep. The "Contraband" Schottische, respectfully dedicated to Major General B. F. Butler, piano (solo) (Oversize 13)
    - Winter, Banks White Wings, vocal (song with chorus) (Oversize 13)
    - Wolf-Ferrari, Ermanno Intermezzo no. 2 from The Jewels of the Madonna, arranged by Otto Langey, violin (solo with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 13)
    - Wood, Haydn I Love to Hear You Singing, words by Lillian Glanville, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (medium voice) (Oversize 13)
    - Wood, Haydn Wonderful World of Romance, words by Harold Simpson, vocal (song) (high voice) (Oversize 13)
    - Woodforde-Finden, Amy Stars of the Desert: Four More Indian Love, lyrics by Laurence Hope, vocal (songs with piano accompaniment) (medium voice) (marked "Mrs. C. R. Vickery – paid- 10-5-23") (Oversize 13)
    - Woodin, William H. Franklin D. Roosevelt March, words by Irving Caesar, piano (solo with vocal trio chorus) (Oversize 13)
    - Woodman, R. Huntington Oh, Blessed Day, poem by Harold Flammer vocal (duet with piano accompaniment) (soprano and tenor) (Oversize 13)
    - Woodman, R. Huntington Two Songs for Voice and Piano: I: Floodgates, poem by Martha Martin, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (high voice) (Oversize 13)
    - Woodman, R. Huntington Songs and Ballads by R. Huntington Woodman: Violets, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (medium voice) (Oversize 13)
    - Wooler, Alfred Consider and hear me, vocal (song) (high voice) two copies, both signed by Winifred S. Myers (Oversize 13)
    - Wooler, Alfred Save Me, O God!, vocal (song) (high voice) two copies (Oversize 13)
    - Wooler, Alfred Someone, words by S. E. Mekin, vocal (duet) (soprano and tenor) (Oversize 13)
    - Worrall, Henry Sebastopol: Descriptive Fantaisie, arranged for guitar by S. S. Stewart, guitar (solo) (Oversize 13)
    - Wright, Kenneth A. The Crab, verses by Dan Cormack, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (signed by "George J. ‘A'ot"[?]) (Oversize 13)
    - Wyman, Addison P. Cantilena: arranged with Brilliant Variations, keyboard (solo) (signed by Jennie L. Butler, B. G. F. Seminary) (Oversize 13)
    - Youmans, Vincent Hallelujah! From Hit The Deck, a Nautical Musical Comedy, book by Herbert Fields, lyrics by Leo Robin & Clifford Grey, Music by Vincent Youmans, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (optional ukulele accompaniment) (Oversize 13)
    - Young, Walter S. A Hymn of Thanksgiving, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (high voice) two copies (Oversize 13)
    - Yradier La Paloma/The Dove, arr. by Trehde, piano (solo) (Oversize 13)
  - Unattributed
    - Annie Laurie: Celebrated Scotch Melody, vocal (song) ("Jennie Lee from cousin E—" written on cover) (Oversize 13)
    - The Hero, keyboard (solo) (Oversize 13)
    - It was a beauteous lady, or, Allan Percy, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 13)
    - Money Musk/A Scotch Reel, keyboard (solo) (Oversize 13)
    - River Waltz, piano (solo) (Oversize 13)
    - Silver Lake Waltz arranged for the piano forte, piano (solo) (Oversize 13)
    - United States Marine March; composed & dedicated to the Officers of the Marine Corps by a Lady of Charlestown, S. C., keyboard (solo) (Oversize 13)
- Bound collections of music
  - Well-known composers
    - Beethoven, Ludwig Sonates pour Piano (Box 1)
    - Chopin, Frédéric Préludes & Rondos (Box 1)
    - Chopin, Frédéric Pianoforte-werke: Band IX: Walzer (Box 1)
    - Clementi, Muzio Sonatinas for Pianoforte (Op. 36, 37, 38), revised and fingered by Louis Koehler, with a biographical Sketch by Philip Hale (Box 1)
    - Grieg, Edvard Lyrische Stücke Heft II / Lyric Pieces Book II, Op. 28 (Box 1)
    - Grieg, Edvard Lyrische Stücke Heft III / Lyric Pieces, Op. 43 (Box 1)
    - Grieg, Edvard Lyrische Stücke Heft IV / Lyric Pieces, Op. 47 (Box 1)
    - Grieg, Edvard Lyrische Stücke Heft V / Lyric Pieces, Op. 54 (Box 1)
    - Grieg, Edvard Lyrische Stücke Heft VI No. 1-3 / Lyric Pieces Vol. VI, No. 1-3, Op. 57 (Box 1)
    - Mendelssohn, Felix Concertos, Midsummer Night's, Walpurgis Night, Altholia (Box 1)
    - Mozart II. (Box 1)
    - Rubinstein, Anton Song Album by Anton Rubinstein, Vol. 1 (Box 2)
    - Schubert, Franz Schubert Compositions II (Box 2)
    - Schubert, Franz 30 Mélodies choisies de Fr. Schubert (Box 2)
    - Schubert – Songs (Box 2)
    - Schumann, Robert Pauer's Edition of R. Schumann's Album (Box 2)
    - Schumann – Symphonies (Box 2)
    - Strauss Overturen zu 4 Händen (Box 2)
    - Wagner Lyrics for Soprano, edited by Carl Armbruster (Box 2)
    - Weber, Carl Maria von Concert Piece, Preciosa, Oberon, by Weber (Box 2)
  - Lesser-known composers
    - Bayer, Edouard 100 recreaciones agradables e instructios sacadas de las mas celebres melodias pour la guitarre par Edouard Bayer/100 recreations agreables et instructive choisies des melodies célèbres pour la guitarre par Edouard Bayer (Book 1) (Oversize 15)
    - Bayer, Edouard 100 recreaciones agradables e instructios sacadas de las mas celebres melodias pour la guitarre par Edouard Bayer/100 recreations agreables et instructive choisies des melodies célèbres pour la guitarre par Edouard Bayer (Book 3) (Oversize 15)
    - Gardana, Enea Transcrizioni per Chitarra di E. Gardana (Oversize 15)
    - Godard, Benjamin Song Album by Benj. Godard, signed by A. L. Osborne (Oversize 15)
    - Loeschhorn Studies for the Piano (Op. 67) (Box 3)
    - Lortzing, Albert Ouvertures pour Piano à 4 mains de Albert Lortzing (Box 3)
  - Various/multiple composers, voice
    - Solo voice
      - Albert Chevalier's Song Album No. 1 (Box 3)
      - Albert Chevalier's Fourth Song Album (Box 3)
      - (No title page, first song is "Nancy Lee" by St. Adams) (Box 3)
      - Selected Opera Gems from Standard Operas Arranged by H. Engelmann (Box 3)
      - Schlag auf Schlag Heft 1 (Box 3)
      - (No title page, first song is I will extol Thee, my God, O King from Abraham by Molique) (Box 3)
      - (No title page, first song is Father in Heaven / Ave Maria by C. Saint Saens) (Box 3)
      - Operatic Anthology – Celebrated Arias Selected from Operas by Old and Modern Composers Edited by Max Spicker – Vol. I, Soprano (Box 3)
      - (No title page, first song is "As when the dove laments her love" from Georg Friedrich Händel's Acis and Galathea) (Box 3)
      - Sacred Songs Selected by Barnby Stebbins, High Voice (Box 3)
      - Music Book and Memories of Madame Sherry (Box 3)
      - Lyric Fancies: A Selection of Songs by American Composers: Volume I, High (Box 3)
      - Masters of Russian Song – Collected and Edited by Kurt Schindler, Vol. II: Twenty-five songs by Balákireff, Tchaïkovsky, Rimsky-Kórsakoff, Borodine, Gretchanínoff and Rachmáninoff (Box 3)
      - (No title page; first song is The Chorister by Arthur S. Sullivan) (Box 3)
      - Fifty Mastersongs by Twenty Composers for Low Voice (Box 4)
      - One Hundred English Folksongs (Box 4)
    - Multiple voices
      - Two-Part Songs for Women's Voices, (Signed by Winifred S. Myers) (Box 4)
      - Choice Sacred Duets: Volume I (Box 4)
      - Sacred Duets for High and Low Voices Compiled and Edited by William Shakespeare (Box 4)
      - Ten Traditional Carols for Christmas Arranged for Men's Voices by Charles Fonteyn Manney (Box 4)
      - Wilson's Sacred Quartets for Mixed Voices (Box 4)
  - Various/multiple composers, instrumental
    - Banjo, mandolin
      - (No title page, first song is "I Love You in the Same Old Way" by J. W. Bratton, arr. by Chas. E. Pratt.) (Box 4)
      - The Whitmark Banjo Folio, Arranged by G. L. Lansing (Signed by Leslie Conrad) (Box 4)
    - Guitar
      - The Guitar Player's Pastime: A Collection of Popular and Standard Airs, Jigs, Reels, Hornpipes, Polkas, Waltzes, Marches, Schottisches and Gems from the Operas (Box 4)
      - Instrumental Guitarist: Choice Collection of Melodies for Guitar by Popular Composers (Box 4)
      - Recherché Collection of Choice Instrumental Guitar Music, (Signed by Wilson) (Box 4)
    - Keyboard
      - Salon-Album für Piano zu 4 Händen (Box 5)
      - E. T. Paull's Folio: Famous Marches No. 1 (Box 5)
      - Classic and Modern Gems for the Reed Organ (Box 5)
      - Choralbuch (Box 5)
      - Sabbath Musings: An Instrumental Collection of Sacred Music for Cabinet Organ or Piano (Box 5)
- Books
  - Instructional books
    - Guitar
      - Esercizio per la Chitarra, contentente 24 Pezzi della maggiore difficoltá, Diversi Preludi, Passaggi ed Assolo composti da Mauro Giuliani (Op. 48) (Box 5)
    - Piano
      - The Synthetic Method for the Pianoforte by Albert Ross Parsons, arranged and developed by Kate S. Chittenden: Exercises in Expansion and Contraction - by Kate S. Chittenden, (signed by David Munson Osborne) (Box 5)
      - The Synthetic Method for the Pianoforte by Albert Ross Parsons, arranged and developed by Kate S. Chittenden: Exercises in Expansion and Contraction - by Kate S. Chittenden, (signed by David Munson Osborne) (Box 5)
      - The Synthetic Method for the Pianoforte by Albert Ross Parsons, arranged and developed by Kate S. Chittenden: Exercises for the Appoggiaturas, Turns and Trills - by Kate S. Chittenden, (signed by David Munson Osborne) (Box 5)
      - Etudes de la Vélocité pour le pianoforte ou Trente Exercises pour devellopper la souplesse et la dexterité des doigts et par venir à exécute les passages les plus rapides - par Charles Czerny (No. 1 – 10) (Box 5)
      - Etudes de la Vélocité pour le piano ou 30 Exercises calcules a devollopper l'agilite des doigts composés - par Charles Czerny (Op. 299) (American Fingering) (Box 5)
      - The Art of Finger Development Op. 740: Book 1 – Czerny (Box 5)
      - Die Schule der Geläufigkeit (l'étude de la vélocité, 40 Exercices, calculés à developper l'agilité des doigts.) 40 Uebungsstücke um die Schnelligkeit der Finger zu entwickeln für das Pianoforte componirt von Carl Czerny – Op. 299 (Heft 3) (Box 5)
      - Exercice Journalier en 40 études pour attendre et conserver le plus haut degré de perfection sur le piano avec des répétitions preserites par Charles Czerny (Op. 337) (Box 5)
      - 12 Etudes de moyenne difficulté pour le piano par Jules Egghard (Op. 84) (Box 5)
      - The Virtuoso Pianist in Sixty Exercises for the Piano Part 1 (by C. L. Hanon) (Box 5)
      - Russell's Choice Editions of Standard Studies for the Piano-Forte – Moschelles' Grand Studies – Part 1 (Op. 70) – German fingering (Box 5)
      - Plaidy's Technical Studies for the Piano Forte – Complete edition (Box 5)
      - American Method for the Piano Forte: Daily Requirements of the Pianist: A Short, Comprehensive and Practical System by Edgar A. Robbins (Box 5)
      - Twenty Studies for the Piano Forte, Composed by Aloise Schmitt (Op. 16) (Box 5)
      - The Daily Exercise for the Pianoforte, Consisting of Scales in Major, and Minor Keys and the Chromatic Scale Ascending and Descending (Box 5)
    - Violin
      - Violin-Schule von Ch. De Bériot – Op. 1102.: Abtheilung I: Elementartechnik: Herausgegeben von Friedrich Hermann (Box 5)
      - Ch. De Beriot's Celebrated Method for the Violin with English and German Text: Part I (Box 5)
      - School for the Violin by Ch. Henning (Op. 15): Part 2 (Box 5)
      - Violin Schoool – Theoretic-practical Course for the Study of the Vionin in two parts by Richard Hofmann (Op. 31) / Violin-Schule – Theoretisch-praktischer Lehrgang zur Erlenung des Violinspiels in zwei Theilen von Richard Hofmann (Op. 31) (Box 5)
      - Tonleiterstudien – Méthode de gammes / Scales studies – violino Solo – by L. H?imaly (Signed by A. Lithgow Osborne) (Box 5)
      - Elementary and Progressive Studies for the Violin – by Kayser, Op. 20, (Signed by David M. Osborne) (Box 5)
      - 36 Etudes élémentaires et progressives pour Violin composées exclusivement pour ceux qui veule se préparer pour les célèbres études de Kerutzer par H. E. Kayser (book 1, Op. 20), (Signed by A. Lithgow Osborne) (Box 5)
      - The School of Violin-Technics – Section I – by Schradieck, (signed by D. M. Osborne) (Box 5)
      - Lagenwechsel-Uebungen (Exercises in Changes of Position) für Violine als Appendix zu jeder Violinschule herausgegeben von Wilhelm Schwendemann – Preis Mk. 3 (Box 5)
      - Die ersten Violin-Uebungen / Premières de Violon / First studies of Violin – von Ad. Grünwald, (signed by David M. Osborne) (Box 5)
    - Voice
      - The Master-pieces of Vocalization – edited by Max Spicker (Box 5)
      - 100 Rounds, Catches, and Canons, for Three and Four Voices – rounds – No. 49 (Box 5)
      - 36 Eight Measure Vocalises for Mezzo Soprano – by Sieber (Op. 93) (Box 5)
    - General
      - Rote Songs of the Normal Music Course, with Accompaniments for the Piano-forte by John W. Tufts (Box 6)
      - Musical Curriculum by George F. Root (Box 6)
  - Institutional books
    - Academies
      - The Songster for Institutes: Public, Private, Preparatory, and Military Schools, Seminaries and Academies by H. J. Taylor (Box 6)
      - Carmina Princetonia (various) (Box 6)
    - Primary school
      - Franklin Square Song Collection – Selected by J. P. McCaskey, two copies (Box 6)
      - Franklin Square Song Collection No. 2 – Selected by J. P. McCaskey (Box 6)
      - Franklin Square Song Collection No. 3 – Selected by J. P. McCaskey (Box 6)
      - Plays and Songs for Kindergarten and Family, collected and revised by a Kindergartner (Box 7)
      - Song Stories for the Kindergarten, by Mildred J. and Patty S. Hill (Box 7)
      - Songs for Little Children for the Kindergartens and Primary Schools, by Eleanor Smith (Box 7)
      - Songs for Little Children Part 1 – A Collection of Songs and Games for Kindergartens and Primary Schools, composed and arranged by Eleanor Smith (Box 7)
      - Songs for Little Children Part 2 – A Collection of Songs and Games for Kindergartens and Primary Schools, composed and arranged by Eleanor Smith (Box 7)
    - Church
      - Singing Pilgrim, by Philip Phillips (Box 7)
      - The New Life Hymnal, edited by John Fair and J. K. Moyer (Box 7)
      - The Beginners' Choir, edited by E. S. Lorenz and Ira B. Wilson (Box 7)
      - The Hall-Mack Company's Book of Anthems No. 2, edited by J. Lincoln Hall (Box 7)
      - The Hall-Mack Company's Book of Anthems No. 3, edited by J. Lincoln Hall, two copies (Box 8)
      - The Jubilate, by L. O. Emerson (Box 8)
      - The New Lute of Zion, by I. B. Woodbury (Box 8)
      - The Key-Note, by William B. Bradbury (Box 8)
      - The Harmonist: being a collection of tunest from the most approved authors, adapted to every variety of metre in the methodist hymn-book and for parochial occasions (no attribution) (Box 8)
      - Sacred Harmony: a collection of music, adapted to the greatest variety of metres now in use, by Samuel Jackson (Box 8)
      - (unreadable title, no attribution readable) (Box 8)
- Opera items
  - Programs
    - Metropolitan Opera House, Grand Opera, 1911-1915
      - 1912, Feb 2 Lucia di Lammermoor – Friday evening (Box 9)
      - 1912, Mar 13 Madama Butterfly – Wednesday afternoon (Box 9)
      - 1913, Mar 21 The Tales of Hoffmann – Friday evening (Box 9)
      - 1915, Feb 12 Boris Godunoff – Friday evening (Box 9)
      - 1915, Feb 19 Die Zauberflöte / The Magic Flute – Friday evening (Box 9)
      - 1915, Feb 26 Euryanthe – Friday evening (Box 9)
    - Metropolitan Opera House, Grand Opera, 1919-1926
      - 1920, Jan 2 Marouf (The Cobbler of Cairo) – Friday Evening (Box 9)
      - 1920, Apr 4 Rossini's Solemn Mass – Sunday evening (Box 9)
      - 1921, Jan 1 Double Bill: L'Amore dei tre Re, Il Carillon Magico / The Magic Chimes – Saturday afternoon (Box 9)
      - 1921, Dec 31 Die Walküre – Saturday afternoon (Box 9)
      - 1923, Mar 10 Mona Lisa – Saturday afternoon (Box 9)
      - 1923, Mar 17 Carmen – Saturday afternoon (Box 9)
      - 1923, Mar 22 Aida – Thursday afternoon (two copies) (Box 9)
      - 1923, Mar 24 Samson et Dalila – Saturday afternoon (Box 9)
      - 1925, Nov 21 L'Africana – Saturday afternoon (Box 9)
  - Libretti
    - L'amore dei tre re - Metropolitan Opera House Grand Opera Libretto, Fred Rullman (Box 9)
    - The Barber of Seville - Grand Opera Libretto, Fred Rullman (Box 9)
    - La Bohème / The Bohemians - G. Ricordi & Co. (Box 9)
    - Boris Godounov – Metropolitan Opera House Grand Opera Libretto, Fred Rullman (Box 9)
    - Il Carillon Magico – Metropolitan Opera House Grand Opera Libretto, Fred Rullman (Box 9)
    - Carmen – Metropolitan Opera House Grand Opera Libretto, Fred Rullman (Box 9)
    - Carmen – Charles F. Tretbar (Box 9)
    - Cavalleria Rusticana – Scotti Grand Opera Co. inc. Libretto, Fred Rullman (Box 9)
    - Euryanthe – Metropolitan Opera House Grand Opera Libretto, Fred Rullman, Inc. (Box 9)
    - La forza del destino – Metropolitan Opera House Grand Opera Libretto, Fred Rullman, Inc. (Box 9)
    - Götterdämmerung / The Dusk of the Gods –Grand Opera Librettos, Oliver Ditson Company (Box 9)
    - La Juive – Chicago Civic Opera Company Libretto, Fred Rullman, Inc. (Box 9)
    - Lucia di Lammermoor – Boston Grand Opera Company Libretto, Charles E. Burden (Box 9)
    - Madam Butterfly – Boston National Grand Opera Company Libretto, Charles E. Burden (Box 9)
    - Magic Flute – Metropolitan Opera House Grand Opera Libretto, Fred Rullman, Inc. (Box 9)
    - Marouf – Metropolitan Opera House Grand Opera Libretto, Fred Rullman, Inc. (Box 9)
    - Mefistofele – Metropolitan Opera House Grand Opera Libretto, Fred Rullman, Inc. (Box 9)
    - Mona Lisa – Metropolitan Opera House Grand Opera Libretto, Fred Rullman, Inc. (Box 9)
    - Operetta Merry-Go-Round, Edward B. Marks Music Corporation (Box 9)
    - L'Oracolo – Scotti Grand Opera Co. Inc. Libretto, Fred Rullman, Inc. (Box 9)
    - Samson et Dalila – Metropolitan Opera House Grand Opera Libretto, Fred Rullman, Inc. (Box 9)
    - Tannhäuser – Charles F. Tretbar (Box 9)
    - Tosca – G. Ricordi & Co. (Box 9)
    - Il Trovatore / The Troubadour – Oliver Ditson Company (Box 9)
    - La Vestale – Metropolitan Opera House Grand Opera Libretto, Fred Rullman, Inc. (Box 9)
    - Die Walkuere – Metropolitan Opera House Grand Opera Libretto, Fred Rullman, Inc., two copies (Box 9)
  - Scores